Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Specifications, correspondence, and other project records, 1891-1985; Series I
  - 13:18 Becton Engineering and Applied Science
    - Department of Engineering Cancer Center, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 760)
    - Luxtrol Light Control Equipment, undated (Box 20, Folder 761)
    - Index of Specifications, undated (Box 20, Folder 762)
    - Electrical Work, undated (Box 20, Folder 763)
  - 14:01 Mason Laboratory
    - Original Specifications, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 764)
    - General, 1935-1969 (Box 21, Folder 765)
    - Alterations, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 766)
    - Renovations, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 767)
    - Mechanical Specifications/HVAC, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 768)
    - Hollow Metal Doors and Frames, Roof Scuttles, Floor Doors, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 769)
    - Submittals: Crane, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 770)
    - Fire Alarm and Clock Systems, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 771)
    - 9660-63-60593 Apparatus: Specifications and Drawings, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 772)
    - Plumbing, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 773)
    - Preliminary Specifications, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 774-777)
    - Final Specifications, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 778-779)
    - Proposed Changes, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 780-785)
    - Electrical Submittals and other Electrical Information, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 786)
    - Daily Field Report I, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 787)
    - Structural Steel Stairs, Manholes, Balcony, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 788)
    - Payne Elevator, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 789)
    - Mail Chute, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 790)
    - Material Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 791)
    - Miscellaneous Specifications, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 792)
    - Sprinkler Drawings, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 793)
    - Crane and Hoist Specifications, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 794)
    - Daily Field Report II, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 795)
    - Air Balancing Report, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 796)
    - ITE Electrical Instructional Booklets, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 797)
    - Transmittals, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 798)
    - Alterations, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 799)
  - 14:08 105 Grove St.
    - Alterations, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 800)
  - 14:09 15 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Heating Specification, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 801)
  - 14:11 1 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Renovations, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 802)
  - 14:15 370 Temple St.
    - Renovations, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 803)
    - Specifications, undated (Box 22, Folder 804)
  - 14:21 Helen Hadley Hall
    - Specifications, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 805-806)
    - Alterations, 1957-1965 (Box 22, Folder 807)
    - Alterations, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 808)
    - Corridor Lighting, undated (Box 22, Folder 809)
  - 14:22 111 Grove St. (Language Laboratory)
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 810)
    - Electrical, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 811)
  - 14:25 University Health Center
    - Specifications: Addenda, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 812)
    - Architectural Specifications, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 813-814)
    - Log and Transmittal File, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 815)
  - 15:02 Hammond Laboratory
    - Air-Conditioning, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 816)
    - Alterations, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 817)
    - Alterations, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 818)
    - Emergency Exits, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 819)
  - 15:09 Berkeley Divinity School
    - Addition Specifications: Plumbing, Heating, Electrical, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 820)
    - Additional Specifications: Special Conditions, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 821)
    - Electrical Alterations, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 822)
    - Urban Hall Shop Drawings, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 823)
  - 15:16 36-38 Mansfield
    - Rental Memorandum, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 824)
  - 15:17 Seeley Mudd Library
    - File 79-38-390, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 825)
  - 16:01 School of Organization and Management
    - Air-Conditioning, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 826)
    - Mechanical and Electrical Specifications, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 827)
    - Project Manual, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 828-829)
    - Project Manual: Street Renovation, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 830-831)
  - 16:02 28 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Specifications, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 832)
  - 16:04 52 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Security System Alterations, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 833)
  - 16:05 77 Prospect St.
    - Renovations, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 834)
  - 16:10 135 Prospect St.
    - Renovations, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 835)
    - New Construction, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 836)
  - 16:11 60 Sachem St. (Astronomy/Computer Center)
    - Heating, Ventilation, Air-Conditioning, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 837)
    - Specifications, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 838-840)
    - Boiler, Burner, Radiation, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 841)
    - Electrical, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 842)
    - Floors, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 843)
    - Hardware, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 844)
    - Plumbing, Kitchen, Shelving, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 845)
    - Shop Drawings, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 846)
    - Miscellaneous Catalogs, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 847)
    - Miscellaneous Details, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 848)
    - Electrical Work, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 849)
    - Alterations: Drawings and Specifications, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 850)
  - 17:02 27 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 851)
  - 17:03 47 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Specifications and Standard Documents, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 852)
  - 17:06 51 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Fire Escape Renovation, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 853)
    - Alterations, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 854)
  - 17:07 55 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Alterations, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 855)
    - Electrical and Lighting Work, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 856)
  - 17:09 43 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Electrical Work, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 857)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 858)
    - Plumbing and Heating, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 859)
    - Renovations, 1937-1938 (Box 24, Folder 860)
    - Landscaping, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 861)
  - 17:10 27 Hillhouse Ave.
    - Electrical, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 862)
  - 17:12 85 Trumbull St.
    - Electric: Lighting, etc., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 863)
  - 18:4-5 155/175 Whitney Ave.
    - Security Lighting, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 864)
    - Security Insurance Building, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 865-866)
    - Specifications, 1924-1967 (Box 24, Folder 867-869)
  - 19:01 Infirmary
    - Alterations, 1891-1905 (Box 24, Folder 870)
  - 19:02 Marsh Hall
    - Alterations, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 871)
    - Greenhouse, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 872)
  - 19:16 230 Prospect St.
    - Fire Code Violations, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 873)
  - 19:17 David S. Ingalls Rink
    - Drawings, Preliminary Estimates, Specifications, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 874-880)
    - Specifications, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 881-882)
    - Scoreboard, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 883)
    - Log and Transmittal File, undated (Box 25, Folder 884)
  - 19:19 Greeley Memorial Laboratory
    - Specifications for Labor and Materials), 1958 (Box 25, Folder 885-886)
    - Heating, Ventilation, and Air-Conditioning, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 887)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 888)
    - Proposed Changes, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 889)
    - Louvers Specifications, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 890)
    - Electrical Specifications, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 891)
    - Miscellaneous Specifications, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 892)
    - Plumbing Specifications, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 893)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 894)
    - Refrigeration, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 895)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 896)
    - Check List, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 897)
    - Parts List, 1960-1964 (Box 25, Folder 898)
    - Electrical Drawings, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 899)
    - Alterations, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 900)
    - Renovations, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 901)
  - 19:21 Married Student Dormitories
    - Mechanical, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 902)
    - Specifications, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 903)
    - Plumbing, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 904)
    - Sound and Television, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 905)
    - Windows and Hardware, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 906)
    - Electrical, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 907)
    - Installation of New Exterior Doors, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 908)
  - 19:22 137 Mansfield St.
    - Renovation, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 909)
  - 19:26 68 Mansfield St.
    - Metering, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 910)
  - 19:30 93-95 Mansfield St.
    - Alterations, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 911)
  - 20:01 Sloan Physics Laboratory
    - Specifications, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 912)
    - Steam Valve Data, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 913)
    - Electrical Work, 1912-1928 (Box 25, Folder 914)
    - Renovations, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 915)
    - Alterations, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 916)
    - Electrical Blueprint, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 917)
    - Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 918)
  - 20:1,5,6,7 Pierson-Sage Square
    - Central Electrical Distribution System, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 919)
  - 20:02 Osborn Laboratory
    - Original Specifications, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 920)
    - Steel and Ironwork, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 921)
    - Masonry Work, 1911-1912 (Box 25, Folder 922)
    - Elevators, 1912 (Box 25, Folder 923)
    - Electrical Work, 1913 (Box 25, Folder 924)
    - Incubator (Freas Thermo Electric Co.), 1928 (Box 25A, Folder 925)
    - Elevators, 1938 (Box 25A, Folder 926)
    - Mechanical Specifications- Botanical/ Zoological Labs, 1945-1946 (Box 25A, Folder 927)
    - Botany Laboratory Renovation, 1962-1963 (Box 25A, Folder 928)
    - Electrical: Rooms 215, 306, 326-324, 1965 (Box 25A, Folder 929)
    - Alterations, 1966 (Box 25A, Folder 930-931)
    - Alterations, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 932-933)
    - Control Environment Room, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 934)
    - Phase II Renovations, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 935)
    - Burton and Van Houten Engineers, Inc.: Specifications for Re-Roofing: Project no. 100-2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 936)
  - 20:03 Pierson-Sage Square
    - Specifications, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 937)
    - Specifications, 1912-1922 (Box 26, Folder 938)
    - Power Plant Refrigeration, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 939)
    - Power Plant Heating Renovations, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 940)
  - 20:05 Sterling Chemical Laboratory
    - General Specifications, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 941)
    - Plumbing, Heating, Ventilation, 1921-1942 (Box 26, Folder 942)
    - Steam Valve Data, 1921-1942 (Box 26, Folder 943)
    - Electrical Work, 1921-1942 (Box 26, Folder 944)
    - Fan Setting and Hood Duct Blueprints, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 945)
    - Kline Addition: Specifications and Drawings, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 946)
    - Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 947-948)
    - Refrigeration Vault, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 949)
    - Renovations to Organic Chemistry Lab, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 950)
    - Renovations to Organic Chemistry Lab-Specifications, 1973 (Box 26A, Folder 951)
    - Renovations to Organic Chemistry Laboratory: Mechanical Manuals, 1973 (Box 26A, Folder 952)
    - Mechanical, 1984 (Box 26A, Folder 953)
    - Third Floor Renovations, undated (Box 26A, Folder 954)
    - Instruction Book and Duplicate Part List for Straight Line Horizontal Heavy-Duty Compressors (2 copies), undated (Box 26A, Folder 955)
  - 20:06 Peabody Museum
    - Electrical Work, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 956)
    - Miscellaneous Specifications, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 957)
    - Equipment Specifications, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 958)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 959)
    - Electrical Work, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 960)
    - Third Floor Renovations, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 961)
    - Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 962-963)
    - Mechanical and Electrical System Renovations, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 964)
  - 20:07 Sage Hall
    - Specifications, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 965-966)
    - Electrical Work, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 967)
    - Air-Conditioning, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 968)
  - 20:07 Bowers Hall
    - Electrical, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 969)
    - Plumbing, Heating, and Ventilation, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 970)
    - General, 1931-1932, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 971)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box 27, Folder 972)
  - 20:08 301 Prospect St. (School of Management)
    - Lighting Alterations, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 973)
  - 20:09 340 Edwards St.
    - Renovations, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 974)
    - Square Footage, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 975)
  - 20:13 Electron Accelerator Laboratory
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building I - Electrical Work, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 976)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building I - Heating and Ventilation, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 977)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building I - Plumbing, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 978)
    - Specifications for Accelerator and Cyclotron Unit, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 979)
    - Excavation and Site Preparation for Accelerator and Cyclotron Unit, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 980)
    - Shepard, Niles, Crane and Hoist Corp, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 981)
    - Cyclotron and Accelerator Unit, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 982)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building II - Concrete and Steel, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 983)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building II - Mechanical Work, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 984)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building II - Heating and Ventilation, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 985)
    - Specifications for Accelerator Building II - Electrical Work, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 986)
    - Specifications for Addition, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 987)
    - Heavy Ion Linear Accelerator - Addition Specifications, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 988)
    - Mechanicals, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 989)
    - Plumbing Fixtures, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 990)
    - Addition, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 991)
    - Specifications for Tandem Accelerator - General, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 992)
    - Specifications for Tandem Accelerator - Heating and Ventilation, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 993)
    - Specifications for Tandem Accelerator - Electrical Work, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 994)
  - 20:13 Electron Accelerator Laboratory (continued)
    - Specifications for Tandem Accelerator - Plumbing, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 995)
    - Renovations, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 996)
    - Accelerator Building, undated (Box 27, Folder 997)
  - 20:14 Josiah W. Gibbs Laboratory
    - Elevators, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 998)
    - Specifications - Electrical, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 999)
    - Specifications - Heating and Ventilation, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1000)
    - Specifications - Mechanical Work, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1001)
    - Hardware, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1002)
    - Incinerators, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1003)
    - Air-Conditioner, 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 1004)
    - Mechanical Binder, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 1005)
    - Electrical Information, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 1006)
    - Sixth Floor Addition - Mechanicals, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 1007)
    - Sixth Floor Addition - Specifications, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1008)
    - Fans, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1009)
    - Specifications File, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1010)
    - Operating and Maintenance Manuals, 1958-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1011)
    - Air-Conditioning, Renovations, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 1012)
    - Alterations, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 1013)
    - Alterations, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1014)
    - Alterations - Preliminary Specifications, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1015-1016)
    - Alterations, Specifications, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1017-1019)
    - Specifications, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1020)
    - Carpentry Hardware, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1021)
    - Mechanical Specifications, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1022)
    - Louvers, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1023)
    - Miscellaneous Iron, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1024)
    - Ventilation, 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1025)
    - Electrical Specifications, 1966-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1026)
    - Fire Warning System, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1027)
    - Chalkboard, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1028)
    - Plumbing, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1029)
    - 15C Laboratory Process Piping, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1030)
    - Air-Conditioning, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1031)
    - Astronomy Alterations -Specifications, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1032)
  - 20:15 Oceanography and Ornithology Laboratory
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1954-1961 (Box 28, Folder 1033)
    - Agreements, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1034)
    - Refrigeration/Air-Conditioning, 1957-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1035)
    - Specifications, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1036-1037)
    - Mechanical/Hardware, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1038)
    - Acoustical, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1039)
    - Architectural Metals, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1040)
    - Carpentry, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1041)
    - Pre-cast Concrete, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1042)
    - Exterior Stone and Flagstone, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1043)
    - Elevators, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1044)
    - Painting Finish Schedule, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1045)
    - Mechanical Specifications: Panels and Louvers, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1046)
    - Miscellaneous Metal, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1047)
    - Masonry, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1048)
    - Limestone Tablet, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1049)
    - Structural, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1050)
    - Hollow Metal Doors and Frames, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1051)
    - Steel Window Sash, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1052)
    - Roofing, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1053)
    - Toilet Partitions, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1054)
    - Opening in Basement Wall, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1055)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 29, Folder 1056)
    - Electrical, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 1057)
    - Plumbing, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 1058)
    - Structural Wall Framing, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1059)
    - Herlex, Disposer and Hopper, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1060)
    - Barstone Counters, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1061)
    - Basement, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1062)
    - Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 1063)
  - 20:16 334 Edwards St.
    - Observatory - Alterations, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1064)
  - 20:18 285 Prospect St.
    - Specifications and Appraisal of Residence, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 1065)
    - Electrical Alterations, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1066)
  - 20:19 Kline Geology Laboratory
    - Miscellaneous Metals, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 1067)
    - Job Meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1068)
    - Fire Alarm System: Edwards Co., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1069)
    - Construction Contract, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1070)
    - Steel Reports, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1071)
    - Sub-Contractors, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1072)
    - Purchase Orders, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1073)
    - Specifications, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1074-1076)
    - Proposed Changes, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1077)
    - Equipment Specifications and Drawings, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1078)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1079)
    - Electrical Drawings and Specifications, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1080)
    - Site Meeting Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1081)
    - Cold Rooms, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1082)
    - Concrete Reports and Tests, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1083)
    - Plumbing Specifications, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1084)
    - Electrical, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1085)
    - Heating and Ventilation (Approved), 1962-1966 (Box 29, Folder 1086)
    - Acoustic Tile, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1087)
    - Capitol Engineering Standards, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1088)
    - Tile Colors, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1089)
    - Costs and Estimates, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1090)
    - Elevator, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1091)
    - Purchase Orders, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1092)
    - Roofing, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1093)
    - Electrical Equipment Specifications, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1094)
    - Letters, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1095)
    - Punch List, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1096)
    - Stone Drawing, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1097)
    - Room Numbering, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1098)
    - Curtis Equipment, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1099)
    - Electrical Work, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 1100)
    - System Performance, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1101)
    - Alterations, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1102)
    - Electrical Work, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1103)
    - Alterations, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1104)
    - Mechanical Specifications, undated (Box 30, Folder 1105)
  - 20:20 Kline Chemistry Laboratory (Added to Sterling)
    - Plumbing Drawings, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1106)
    - Electrical Equipment Specifications, 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 1107)
    - Plumbing Specifications, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 1108)
    - Electrical Drawings, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1109)
    - Acid-proof Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1110)
    - Elevator Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1111)
    - Miscellaneous Lighting/Electrical Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1112)
    - General Electric Lighting/Electric Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1113)
    - Dual-Lite Electrical Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1114)
    - Fire Alarm Specifications, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 1115)
    - Miscellaneous Drawings and Specifications, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 1116)
    - Air-Conditioning and Ventilation Compressors, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1117)
    - Fixture Cuts, undated (Box 30, Folder 1118)
    - Wall Case Instructions, undated (Box 30, Folder 1119)
  - 20:21 Nuclear Structures Laboratory
    - Renovations, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 1120)
  - 20:23 Kline Biology Tower
    - Accounts and Schedules, 1958-1968 (Box 30, Folder 1121)
    - Environmental Chambers, Pumps, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1122)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1123)
    - Laboratory Fixtures, Control System, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1124)
    - Environmental, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1125)
    - Mechanical, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1126)
    - Environmental Conditions Alarm, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1127)
    - Environmental Growth Chambers and Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1128)
    - Laboratory Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1129)
    - Laboratory Equipment, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 1130)
    - Zetlin Field Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1131)
    - Purchase Lists, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1132)
    - Toilet Room Accessories, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1133)
    - Waterproofing, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1134)
    - Roofing, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1135)
    - Site, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1136)
    - Television, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1137)
    - Telephones, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1138)
    - Underground Addition, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1139)
    - Time and Material Charge Report, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1140)
    - Relative Humidity Readings, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1141)
    - Sheet Metal Work, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1142)
    - Quarterly Report, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1143)
    - Purchase Orders, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1144)
    - Weekly Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 1145)
    - Purchase Orders After 1-11-67, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1146)
    - Alterations, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1147)
    - Purchase Orders, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 1148)
    - Building Curtailment and Safety Concerns, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1149)
  - 20:24 354 Edwards St.
    - Specifications, 1899 (Box 31, Folder 1150)
  - 20:25 Pierson-Sage Parking Structure
    - Specifications, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1151)
    - Lighting Fixtures, 1970-1977 (Box 31, Folder 1152)
  - 21:04 Observatory
    - Heliostat Building, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 1153)
  - 21:06 Divinity School
    - Specifications, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 1154-1155)
    - Specifications, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 1156)
    - Mechanical/Electrical, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 1157)
    - Heating and Boiler Room Specifications, 1931-1949 (Box 31, Folder 1158)
    - Buildings A-E, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 1159-1161)
    - Housing Specifications, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 1162)
    - Renovations, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1163)
    - Renovations, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1164)
    - The Hinchman Company: Construction Specifications for Cathodic Protection System, Miscellaneous Documentation, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 1165)
    - The Hinchman Company: Cathodic Protection Contract Bids, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 1166)
    - The Hinchman Company: Engineering the Cathodic Protection for Heating and Hot Water Piping, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1167)
    - The Hinchman Company: Memos and Correspondence concerning Inspection of Cathodic Protection, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1168)
  - 22 Medical Center
    - Electrical Specifications, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 1169)